// All quiz questions

const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "How many seasons of 'Friends' were there?",
        a: "5",
        b: "10",
        c: "15",
        d: "20",
        answer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What name does Ross mistakenly say at the altar when he's about to marry Emily?",
        a: "Phoebe",
        b: "Emma",
        c: "Rachel",
        d: "Monica",
        answer: "Rachel",
    },
    {
        question: "Which character had a spin off series set in LA?",
        a: "Joey",
        b: "Chandler",
        c: "Monica",
        d: "Rachel",
        answer: "Joey",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the blond haired barista at Central Perk?",
        a: "Gintars",
        b: "Phoebe",
        c: "Gunther",
        d: "Janice",
        answer: "Gunther",
    },
    {
        question: "What animal does Rachel run into when she attempts to jog like Phoebe?",
        a: "fox",
        b: "dog",
        c: "cow",
        d: "horse",
        answer: "horse",
    },
    {
        question: "Which actor stars opposite Joey in a WW1 movie?",
        a: "Gary Oldman",
        b: "Jeff Goldblum",
        c: "Hugh Laurie",
        d: "Bruce Willis",
        answer: "Gary Oldman",
    },
    {
        question: "How many sisters does Joey have?",
        a: "3",
        b: "5",
        c: "7",
        d: "9",
        answer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What colour is the main sofa in Central Perk?",
        a: "yellow",
        b: "purple",
        c: "red",
        d: "orange",
        answer: "orange",
    },
    {
        question: "Which actress plays Phoebe?",
        a: "Jennifer Aniston",
        b: "Lisa Kudrow",
        c: "Ellen DeGeneres",
        d: "Courteney Cox",
        answer: "Lisa Kudrow",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of Ross' first wife?",
        a: "Emily",
        b: "Susan",
        c: "Rachel",
        d: "Carol",
        answer: "Carol",
    },
    {
        question: "How many pages were in the letter that Rachel wrote to Ross?",
        a: "6",
        b: "12",
        c: "18",
        d: "24",
        answer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "Which Caribbean island do the group travel to for Ross' convention in Season 9?",
        a: "Barbados",
        b: "Jamaica",
        c: "Cuba",
        d: "The Bahamas",
        answer: "Barbados",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ross' monkey?",
        a: "Marty",
        b: "Mandy",
        c: "Maurice",
        d: "Marcel",
        answer: "Marcel",
    },
    {
        question: "What instrument does Phoebe play?",
        a: "Guitar",
        b: "Piano",
        c: "Flute",
        d: "Keyboard",
        answer: "Guitar",
    },
    {
        question: "What caused the fire in Phoebe and Rachel's apartment?",
        a: "Candles",
        b: "Hair straightener",
        c: "Electrical fault",
        d: "Hair curler",
        answer: "Hair straightener",
    },
    {
        question: "What is Phoebe's twin sister called?",
        a: "Erica",
        b: "Janine",
        c: "Kathy",
        d: "Ursula",
        answer: "Ursula",
    },
    {
        question: "Who did Phoebe dress up as for Monica's Halloween party?",
        a: "Catwoman",
        b: "Supergirl",
        c: "Spiderwoman",
        d: "Batgirl",
        answer: "Supergirl",
    },
    {
        question: "How many towel categories does Monica have?",
        a: "3",
        b: "5",
        c: "8",
        d: "11",
        answer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What do the bullies at the coffee shop steal from Chandler?",
        a: "His watch",
        b: "His hat",
        c: "His wallet",
        d: "His jacket",
        answer: "His hat",
    },
    {
        question: "What nationality is Emily?",
        a: "British",
        b: "Canadian",
        c: "Chinese",
        d: "Australian",
        answer: "British",
    },
    {
        question: "What does Rachel have a tattoo of on her hip?",
        a: "A star",
        b: "A butterfly",
        c: "A heart",
        d: "A moon",
        answer: "A heart",
    },
    {
        question: "How many episodes of Friends were there in total?",
        a: "179",
        b: "236",
        c: "304",
        d: "368",
        answer: "236",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the one state that Ross forgot when he was playing the '50 states game'?",
        a: "South Dakota",
        b: "Illinois",
        c: "Missouri",
        d: "Delaware",
        answer: "Delaware",
    },
    {
        question: "What was Mike's profession before becoming a professional pianist?",
        a: "Lawyer",
        b: "Teacher",
        c: "Doctor",
        d: "Accountant",
        answer: "Lawyer",
    },
    {
        question: "What does Phoebe find floating in a can of soda in Season 1?",
        a: "A thumb",
        b: "A cockroach",
        c: "$20",
        d: "A secret note",
        answer: "A thumb",
    },
]